Good morning.
Don't make eye contact with him.
He's the scariest person ever.
hello anyone here she wearing a nun's habit
what's this kid doing in here oh look i just caught the school thug molesting an innocent
little girl on camera scandalous codica talk about disgusting what am not i guess we'll
just have to let the people who see this be the judge huh what websites do you think i
should put it on but why would you do that to me
yozara mikazaki sister maria hello allow me to welcome you to my club room what do you mean your
room it was my special nap time room before you lied and then stole it from me i take it you know
each other i told you about her maria takiyama is a nun who works at the school and happens to be
our club's faculty advisor what but she's just a little kid don't call me little i am a legitimate
teacher how old are you anyway 10 years old you do look your age okay so you said something about
her stealing this room from you yes that's right she attacked me while i was napping she came up to me
and slapped me on my right cheek for no reason and she said so sayeth the lord but whosoever
strikes you on the right cheek turn to him the other also then she smacked me on my left cheek too
it hurt really bad then she said so sayeth the lord but whosoever strikes you on the right cheek
offer up to them your room you shall sign their club founding documents and also grant unto them
your sealeth of faculty approval i checked later but it turns out what she told me isn't anywhere in
the bible liar falsifier booby head wow i can't believe you fell for that it was terrifying i was
afraid if i refused to do it she would slap me again well that makes sense she probably would have
hey who the heck are you anyway my name's kotika hasagawa i'm a member of the club so you two are
yours are his minions huh hello rude um i am a minion to no one thank you very much yeah what she just
said meet over there has absolutely nothing to do with me she's not even a member i am so a member
shut up it doesn't really matter because this room is mine i'm quitting being the faculty advisor to
this club right now everybody get out i figured you'd do this i mean you are just a child what did you say
huh it simply wasn't fair of me to expect a child to behave like she was an adult i feel so stupid
now i should have asked a grown-up instead i'm sure they would have never simply quit a job they had
promised to do what don't say that i'm grown up poor thing got in over her head bummer i assumed a little
girl genius like sister maria would have been able to handle this like a professional but i was sorely
mistaken i'm a full-grown adult i could be faculty advisor to this club in my sleep come on you don't
have to prove yourself to us what no that's not what i'm doing at all oh does that mean you still
want to be our advisor of course it does well then bow your head and say please let me be your faculty
advisor please let me be your faculty advisor now you're gonna have to let me do whatever i want to do
in this room and you need to swear to god i swear also if you ever tell me again that you're going
to quit you won't mind if i strip you naked take pictures and spread them all over the internet
no i won't really how nice let's have a round of applause for our new advisor maria takiyama
come on this is where you clap oh yay you guys are embarrassing me don't worry i'll take care of
everything stupid we're gonna need you to clean the room every other day but at the moment i'm thirsty
so some tea would be great i'll get it there's nothing easier than fooling a fool am i right guys
somebody's watching you yeah at least i have this weird feeling i'm being watched
you i wonder if maybe it's a stalker
kotika are you serious i mean think about it for a second 90 of stalkers stalk because they think
they're in love with their victim have you had anything remotely resembling a romance since coming
to the school shut up first that's not true and b i shouldn't have asked hold on just a second
i'm not about to let a fellow club member suffer alone today's club focus helping you let's catch
your stalker
yep i'm definitely getting the feeling we're being watched truth this was not just your imagination
kotika what's happening now is not what i was talking about i don't know why but every single
person we pass has given me the freaking evil eye how am i supposed to find a stalker with this crap going
on center's abandoned me for a criminal man white nice guys have to finish last oh you're jealous
duh you're wrong this isn't how it looks i've seen this in movies you know where the scary guy says
what are you looking at and freaks everyone out i've never seen it in real life before though
they were the ones who wanted to come along why do i always have to be the bad guy
what's up stalker
what the hell is that i'm giving you my wallet this is your standard shakedown isn't it no
my name is yukimura kusunoki i'm in class one one wait isn't that a famous samurai's name that's right
he's from the warring states period my parents chose it for me because they wanted me to become
a son they could be proud of just like yukimura sonata's parents had been a son really yes i'm
obviously a boy so that would make sense uh you are not obviously anything so what's the deal with
following me around all the damn time to tell you the truth i'm a sad victim of bullying bullying you guys
have bullies at this school i didn't know how could you not there are no schools without bullies
what are they bullying you about or do you even know they do it because it's fun it's fun
people just enjoy attacking others when they know they're not going to get hurt in the process
like killing living animals or torturing somebody online but it's the person who's getting bullied's
fault the bully would stop if they wouldn't react and give them something to enjoy and that's straight
from the horse's mouth how dare you assume i'm the same as those cowards
anyway what's the deal how come you were following kotika right well everybody is afraid of him so i
thought i could study him and learn how to become strong for real you think this awkward chicken is
strong excuse me he lives life by his very own set of rules and does whatever he wants to do
whenever he wants to do it he's brave yet feared he takes what he wants from whomever but isn't greedy
and he gets rid of people who refuse to do what he says all while being surrounded by gorgeous ladies
who do his bidding he neither knows nor shows fear of god because he is the lord of his own heaven and
earth that dude is from a different anime i always follow school rules and have never stolen anything
women do not serve me add modesty to that list someone help let's break this down the bottom line
is you are trying to become someone who would never get bullied how do people bully you in the first
place the boys in my class leave me out of whatever they're doing all the time like for example when
we've got gym every time i start to change my clothes they run off as fast as they can it's so mean
and when we play dodgeball they never even try to hit me um how's that bad poor yukimura that's the
saddest thing i've ever heard i'm pretty sure they treat me this way because they're all convinced i'm
a girl but i just know it'll stop if i become manlier like you kotika you are an inspiration not a lot of
people are willing to face their difficulties head-on like you do it's brave i think you should thoroughly
study the art of becoming a man with our resident thug that's so sweet of you however
kotika is very busy with our neighbors club activities if you were to join the group as well
then you'd get the chance to observe him in his natural habitat i'm so in why didn't you treat me
like that when i joined okay what's your angle fess up what's the big problem you're getting your own
personal underling this way you'll be the consummate delinquent why would i want that do you really mean it
i'm gonna be kotika's personal underling that makes me very happy may i call you my big brother
sometimes uh sure kid do what you want
so it turns out this 10 year old is not only a teacher but our group advisor and then a boy who
you'd swear was a girl ended up joining the club isn't that crazy it seems like the only thing you ever
talk about now is that club what you upset about that no way that's the dumbest thing i've ever heard
racist v felicity sumeragi would never allow her feathers to be ruffled absurd yeah yeah make sure
to clean your plate what is all this a little snack yozra helped me out with it she said if i wanted to be
a good underling i should provide you with food and comic books so that's what i did that girl defines
irresponsible i hope you enjoy it big brother tell me you just saw that apparently he's preying on
freshmen now too he made that kid by all this hey hold up damn it since joining the stupid neighbors
club my reputation has gotten even worse hey are you okay
this comic is actually pretty good i gotta remember to pay yukimura back later
he's a normal second year boy except he looks mean and his hair is the same color as dirty dishwater
excuse me are you the one who carried rika to the nurse's office earlier rika that's correct rika
shigama specifically rika's very glad she found you she's in her first year i get it yeah i was
the one who carried you thank you for saving rika's life it was very kind of you oh uh yeah don't worry
about it rika cannot not worry about it you are rika's savior and that is a big deal rika feels she
must repay you with a price that is equal to rika's own life wait your life are you telling me the chemicals
in those beakers were dangerous oh no not especially it was only a quick acting sleeping
drug so rika can say it was safe so pretty much i didn't save your life at all perhaps rika's life
wasn't technically in mortal danger however had you not taken rika to the nurse's office so quickly
who knows what horrible and tragic things could have been done to rika while she was so defenseless
horrible things things like rape what you just said rape that is generally the kind of thing
which happens in the books rika is fond of reading some strange men could have come into
the lab while rika was sleeping and lustfully ripped off all of her clothing and then one after
another in their carnal frenzy they might have ravaged rika's delicate body pounding her wildly
with their wicked desires come with me sure okay
what the hell rika why are you talking about rape right rika probably shouldn't talk about it in front
of others nevertheless rika feels the need to give you a token of gratitude for rescuing her chastity
thanks but no nonsense perhaps rika can fix your silly looking hair that is not a good dye job at all
this is my real hair what it's true my mom was english and blonde and it's the only thing i have
left of her i'm never changing it ow what'd you do that for because rika is very interested in your dna
what interested how rika has to go back to the science lab now the science lab yes rika's a science lab
student i didn't know they had those they do it's a special program for kids like rika
so they don't get picked on you mean that you
i see things aren't easy for you either oh please don't look at rika with such kind eyes you're making
rika blush um by the way rika still does not know your name right my name is kotaka kotaka it's very nice
nice to meet you
hey it seems for the first time in rika's life she has an interest in mammals
excuse me i brought you some coffee uh excuse me but why are you wearing a maid uniform
you're a dude it's part of my special training to help make him a real man what nothing you said
makes sense yozra has been so sweet and helpful just this morning she told me real men exude a
raw masculinity that simply cannot be hidden or disguised no matter what they may do say or wear
why are you torturing the poor kid like that you know speaking of torture i heard a nasty rumor you
like totally raved a freshman i really am a true i did not please that girl was just awkward because
she spends all day in the science lab alone oh is that right hey i just remembered i know about that
girl you helped she's a genius inventor named rika shiguma i heard that since she was a kid she's been
creating all kinds of things like electronics computer programs and medicines she's even provided
technology to giant corporations daddy convinced her to enroll here but she doesn't actually go to any
classes she just invents stuff all day she really doesn't have to go to class that's right just
goes to the lab in fact the only reason the science lab was created was for her to use they're treating
that girl like a vip not fair how is it acceptable to treat her so much better uh because it's normal
for the superior to be given preferential treatment over the mediocre i still have yet to
figure out why they haven't built me my own room too here you go thank you
well finally rika has found you oh hey did you need something after a bit of research rika discovered
you belong to this neighbor's club rika thought she might join too she what uh rika already signed
the application listen rika or whatever you may not know but this club exists for an extremely noble
purpose to be accepted you're going to have to meet certain requirements like wanting to make friends
that is the purpose of the club is it not how did you know because rika read your official poster
friends wanted was clearly written across it diagonally you mean you could actually read
that on the poster and it seems rika was correct if the requirement is not having friends rika is
confident she qualifies yep that's pretty much all it takes to get in here
all right starting today you're a member welcome to the club now rika will be able to see kodaka
every day after school not that rika isn't excited to meet the rest of you that is as long as you
don't get in rika's way of kodaka of course and you told me she was awkward hey something in your
pocket is hurting me oh rika is sorry she forgot all about the dirty book she left there a dirty book
how can you just walk around with it like that easy so you want to see it you show it to people
of course why wouldn't i it really gets rika going wait isn't that just a regular robot manga
how's that supposed to be dirty what you mean you haven't heard of zizi unit number two before
oh yeah how do you like the taste that's my prized high mega bazooka unit number two oh zizi it's so fat
and hard i can't believe this it went all the way inside oh it's incredible tell me more you can't
stand it when i attack you there can you get ready i'm preparing to pierce your dt field now oh no
it's my first time so oh please be gentle on me i don't think your huge dual equipped mega beam
cannon is going to fit it's just too big
i can't hold out any longer energy 170 percent i'm fully charged here it comes
yes right here
i'm gonna shudder it feels like you're about to break me in half
ah i can tell the heat from you is deep inside of me
ah ah
you need
cool
every time rika reads it it is like the first time rika's favorite part is both of the robot's
expressions when they reach their final climax simultaneously there aren't many artists talented
enough to express that kind of satisfaction you are messed up you do not have to understand it rika
does not expect that from you but that doesn't mean she'll give in hey would you like to try sexual
intercourse with rika what the what are you doing you can't just ask someone to do that like that
please calm down there's no reason to get upset rika knows for a fact friends with benefits are all
the rage these days no that's not a real thing how cute you're so innocent it's sweet well anyway you
can't do that kind of thing because um we don't allow inappropriate friendships in this club all right
but don't you think men and women can be normal friends and still have sex too absolutely not
hey um what's the matter yosara nothing i'm fine it appears rika has accidentally stepped on a
landmine still from now on rika thinks we should try new things together don't you agree why am i
feeling this fresh ache in my heart why did she have to go and read that damn poster what's her deal
with him anyway it's like she thinks he's gonna be her new best friend uh were you talking no hey
hey don't look at us
Kodaka, will you please give Rika your jeans?
Will you put them inside, please?
Put them inside what?
Inside Rika's lab test tube.
You already took my hair, didn't you?
You said your hair was all you had left of your mother, right?
Yes. The blonde is because she was English,
but my dad is just your average Japanese guy.
But Rika thought all half-Japanese people were pretty.
Well, they're not.
Kobito inherited all the cute jeans.
Who's that?
Next. This time, the saga is a serious battle.
Wait, tell Rika who Kobito is right now!
...
What's ...